<!-- copied from the fandom wiki -->

<content>



    <section name="Basic info">
        The Summoner is an AI-controlled Boss in Diep.io added on 19th August 2016. It shares similarities with the Fallen Overlord, but has a Square body and peach-colored Square Drones as its spawn. Excluding Maze, it has a 1/5 chance to spawn after every 45 minutes has elapsed since the server's opening if a Boss is not yet present. It is similar to the Necromancer by shape only, as it spawns Drones for itself, and neither does the Summoner nor its Drones take a Square as one of its own when bumping into one.
    </section>



    <section name="Behavior">
        <b>Passive</b>
        On spawn, the Summoner will take the shortest route to the border of the arena, where it will then circle around the arena by a predetermined path either clockwise or counterclockwise. The Boss itself passively spins either clockwise or counterclockwise and completes one full rotation every 24 seconds. The Summoner is neutral to all players unless provoked by damage, in which will set off its Aggressive behavior.

        <b>Aggressive</b>
        When the Summoner is provoked, the player that damaged it will be marked as a target by only a frame for any of its Square Drones currently alive to chase after if not yet already locked on to one.

        <b>Miscellaneous</b>
        The Summoner is not targeted by Base Drones in a team Game Mode unless it provokes them, the Summoner also ignores them entirely even while being attacked. the Base itself does not inflict damage as it passes through.
    </section>



    <section name="Strategy">
        N/A
    </section>



    <section name="Trivia">
        - It is the second AI-controlled Boss added to the game; the first being the Guardian.
        
        - An hour after being added to the game, the developer created a thread for players to suggest the name of this new Boss. It would then later be named "Summoner." Other prominent name suggestions which never made it were "Lich", "Necrolord", "Alpha Square" and, jokingly, "Anokuu."
        
        - The Summoner's max Drone capacity is equivalent to a Necromancer with 3 points invested in Drone Count.
        
        - If the Summoner were to lose all its drones at once, it would take just 1.4 seconds to replenish all the drones it had lost.
        
        - The Summoner shares the same color to not just Yellow Squares but also neutral Dominators, Arena Closers, and both Trap and Bullet projectiles fired from the Defender.
        
        - The color can be reproduced using hex code #ffe869
        
        - The Summoner as a whole can safely fit inside the body of a Dominator.
        
        - Despite Summoner and Fallen Overlord being virtually identical to each other (apart from their appearances and other small differences), the Summoner is the harder Boss to fight against as its Square drones are slightly larger and take up more area, making it more difficult for one to effectively land hits on the body through its drone cloud.
        
        - The Summoner is likely based on the Necromancer, as it uses Necromancer drones (undead Squares) and looks like a Square with Spawners.
    </section>



    
</content>