<content>

    <section name="Gunner Info">
        Gunner is a tier 3 tank that can be selected upon reaching level 30 using "Machine Gun", and at level 45, can be upgraded into "Auto Gunner", "Gunner Trapper" and "Streamliner".
    </section>

    <section name="Meta builds">
        <builds>
            1. <build points="0/0/0/5/7/7/7/7"/>
            Alternatives:
            2. <build points="0/0/0/7/7/7/7/5"/>
            3. <build points="0/0/0/7/7/7/5/7"/>
        </builds>
    </section>

    <section name="Strategy">
        - Gunner has surprisingly high DPS, use this to get close to enemies and push them away.

        - When attacking low health enemies spread your bullets in that area minimising possible dodges and increasing chances of hitting your target.

        - Gunner is a fragile tank prioritise keeping your health high over dealing damage.
    </section>

    <section name="Trivia">
        - In older versions, Gunner used to be able to upgrade into the old removed Auto Tank, and then Auto 5 when it was replaced.
        
        - All Gunner upgrades are not unique to it, as they can be selected from other tanks.

        - Previously, it could upgrade into the Auto Tank and its successor Auto 5.
        
        - Until July 31st, 2016, the Gunner was the only Tier 3 tank in Diep.io without an upgrade, but on August 1st, 2016, the Gunner received its first upgrade, the Auto Gunner, Later that day,  Gunner Trapper was also made an upgrade to it.
        
        - A few hours after the Streamliner was released, it was also made a Gunner upgrade.
        
        - Although its Bullets look like the smallest in-game, when compared a Level 45 Gunner with a Level 45 Gunner Trapper, the Bullets of Gunner Trapper are even smaller, but due to the fact that the Gunner is a Tier 3 tank, and it is mostly used at lower Levels, its Bullets are considered as the smallest. A Level 30 Gunner fires the smallest Bullets in-game as long as it’s not leveled up.
        
        - Machine Gun II could have been a possible placeholder for Gunner, as Machine Gun II was removed when Gunner was added.
    </section>
    
</content>
