<content>

    <section name="Smasher Info">
        Smasher is a tier 3 tank that can be selected upon reaching level 30 with "Basic Tank", and at tier 4, can be upgraded into "Landmine", "Auto Smasher", and "Spike".
    </section>

    <section name="Meta Builds">
        1. <build points="3/10/10/10"/>
        Alternatives:
        2. <build points="5/9/9/10"/>
    </section>

    <section name="Strategy">        
        - Players risk getting killed ramming another Smasher if they both are at max health and have Max Health and Body Damage at the same level.

        - Keep your health high, due to it not having any other forms of offence or defence it need to have high HP to be able to survive.

        - Constantly change direction while dodging to avoid bullet clumps.

        - Allow enemies chasing you to get close without taking damage to so they have less time to react when you go to ram them.

        - Players flinch when chasing a smasher class, use this to your advantage when retreating, make them think you're attempting to kill when you're just wanting space.
        
        - Use enemies recoils to your advantage.

        - Scavage kills off others and third party other playersand escape after getting the kill.
    </section>

    <section name="Trivia">
        - A Level 45 Smasher with fully upgraded Max Health has 338 HP.
        
        - This is one of the six tanks that automatically has auto spin activated, the others being the Landmine, Spike, Auto Smasher, Auto 3 and Auto 5.
        
        - Smasher is the only tier-3 tank to skip a tier.
        
        - On the legacy mobile version, any tank branching off from the Smasher including itself once upgraded to, the shoot button would disappear. However, if one is to touch the button as if it is there, the minimap showing the direction of the player would still move despite the button being invisible.
        
        - Smasher's shell is rotated slightly counterclockwise with respect to where the front of the tank should be in its upgrade icon and the class tree. This can be seen easier in the Auto Smasher upgrade icon.
    </section>
    
</content>
