<content>

    <section name="Tri-Angle Info">
        Tri-Angle is a tier 3 tank that can be selected upon reaching level 30 using "Flank Guard", and at level 45, can be upgraded into "Booster" and "Fighter".
    </section>

    <section name="Meta Builds">
        1. <build points="0/0/0/5/7/7/7/7"/>
        2. <build points="0/2/3/0/7/7/7/7"/>
        Alternatives:
        3. <build points="0/1/2/2/7/7/7/7"/>
        4. <build points="5/7/7/0/0/0/7/7"/>
    </section>

    <section name="Strategy">
        - When low HP either try to block the bullets with your own or try to dodge and retreat as back bullets don't deal much damage.
        
        - Depending on you're bullet speed try to group as many bullets in front of your tank, to create a wave of bullets that pushes enemies to eventual death.

        - Use your consistent high recoil to your advantage by dodging masses of damage and escaping dangerous threats easier.
    </section>

    <section name="Trivia">
        - At level 30, Tri-Angle is the fastest tank in the game, if both reload and movement speed are maxed out.
        
        - Tri-Angle and its upgrades had desynced front, back and/or side barrels, this allowed it to increase its DPS by stacking their bullets. It was mostly used as a defence mechinism for extra recoil and damage against an aggressor, it also allowed an offence angle mainly used against slower tanks because of the high recoil pushing them further away. This was removed in most modes during May of 2025, and later Maze, it is yet to be removed in Sandbox. Being able to flipfire accurately and consistently took practise and skill to which gave the tank a very high skill ceiling which not many tanks have.
        
        - There was a recent bug where the achievements you got the for upgrading into Tri-Angle and Flank Guard were switched. This was because their ID numbers were switched to patch "Triflank" in sandbox, however the achievements were still attached to the original ID.
        
        - Unlike other classes, the Tri-Angle branch is more flexible with the builds they can use.
    </section>

</content>
